(Howard:)left him when
he was 11.
(Penny:)Okay, I will think about it.
(Howard:)You know, I've always
blamed myself
(Howard:)for him leaving.
(Howard:)I always thought it was because
I wasn't the son he wanted.
(Penny:)Yeah, I said I'd
think about it.
(Howard:)I wasn't athletic,
yeah, I was kind of sickly...
(Penny:)Okay, fine. Look, look,
I'm calling her now! See?!
(Howard:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)So anyway,
Howard asked Penny
(Leonard:)to talk to Bernadette,
and she did,
(Leonard:)and Bernadette agreed to meet
him for a cup of coffee.
(Katee Sackhoff:)One question.
Yeah?
(Sheldon:)Why on earth
are you telling me all this?
(Howard:)I don't know.
(Leonard:)Sometimes your movements
are so lifelike,
(Leonard:)I forget you're
not a real boy.